{
    "subject": "resource/2000_Mountain_West_Conference_Baseball_Tournament",
    "predicate": "property/rd3Team",
    "object": "Utah",
    "human_readable": "The team participating in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament is Utah.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.98795086145401,
            "question": "Was Utah a participant in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9871095418930054,
            "question": "Name the team that competed in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9776844382286072,
            "question": "Which team participated in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.938977062702179,
            "question": "Which team won the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8789174556732178,
            "question": "In what tournament did Utah compete in the year 2000?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8360655903816223,
            "question": "What conference was involved in the 2000 Baseball Tournament?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7445081472396851,
            "question": "What year was the Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament held?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5296695828437805,
            "question": "Besides baseball, what other sports might be part of the Mountain West Conference?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45958438515663147,
            "question": "Are there other conferences similar to the Mountain West Conference?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21827444434165955,
            "question": "What other events might occur alongside a college baseball tournament?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The team participating in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament is Utah.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1674_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other conferences similar to the Mountain West Conference?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1674_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Besides baseball, what other sports might be part of the Mountain West Conference?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1674_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year was the Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament held?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1674_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1674_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents provide information about Utah's participation and performance in the 2000 Mountain West Conference Baseball Tournament, thus supporting the statement that Utah was one of the teams participating in the 2000 tournament."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}